<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gallery>
    <image>
        <title>Fractional Currency Shield</title>
        <url>images/Fractional Currency Shield.jpg</url>
        <description>Fractional currency shields such as this were produced by the US Treasury between June 1866 and May 1869.  The Treasury planned to place them in banks where they would be used to authenticate the fractional paper money then in circulation.  Because banks were expected to purchase the shields they were never widely distributed.</description>
    </image>
    <image>
        <title>Sport Touring</title>
        <url>images/Sport Touring.jpg</url>
        <description>This watercolor of a 1929 Marmon automobile is the work of Charles Hubbell (1898-1971) of Cleveland.  Hubbell would go on to a career as a nationally noted aviation artist, perhaps, best recognized for the aviation calendars he produced for Thompson Products/TRW.</description>
    </image>
    <image>
        <title>Tomlinson Hall</title>
        <url>images/Tomlinson Hall.jpg</url>
        <description>This architectural rendering (1945) of Tomlinson Hall on the CWRU campus is from the studio of Walker and Weeks. Walker and Weeks was one of Cleveland's most notable architectural firms. Its works, executed largely between the 1910s and 1950s form a substantial part of the city's architectural legacy.</description> 
	</image>
	<image>
		<title>Phillis Wheatley</title> 
		<url>images/Phillis Wheatley.jpg</url>
		<description>Phillis Wheatley (1753-1784) was the first published African-American poet. Born a slave, Wheatley would become free in 1773; her freedom being a consequence of the popularity of her works in both the American colonies and England.</description>
	</image>
	<image>
		<title>St. Elizabeth's</title> 
		<url>images/StElizabeths.jpg</url>
		<description>Kalman Kubinyi (1906-1973) was considered as Cleveland's preeminent print maker. This print of St. Elizabeth's Church on lower Buckeye Road reflects upon Kubinyi's heritage as he was born in the Hungarian community in the Buckeye neighborhood.</description>
	</image>
	<image>
		<title>Strike</title>
		<url>images/Strike.jpg</url>
		<description>Grant Hamilton (1862-1926) was a political cartoonist best known for his work relating to the elections in the 1890s and early 1900s.   This cartoon, which focuses on Democratic Presidential candidate William Jennings Bryan and the free silver issue is typical of his work at that time, which in the main, promoted the candidates and platforms of the Republican Party.</description>
	</image>
	<image>
		<title>Strike that Failed</title>
		<url>images/Strike that Failed.jpg</url>
		<description>During World War II, the CIO made several attempts to organize the workers at Thompson Products (later to become TRW, Inc.).   The Cleveland-based company, headed by Frederick C. Crawford, had its own, internal labor union and each organizational drive was defeated.   This cartoon reflects on the patriotic motives of the workers in refusing to join the CIO.   </description>
	</image>
	<image>
		<title>Pyramid of Capitalist System</title>
		<url>images/Pyramid of Capitalist System.jpg</url>
		<description>The Socialist Party was a highly visible part of Cleveland's political scene during the late nineteenth and early twentieth centuries.  These two prints, both dating from 1912, were issued by the International Publishing Company in Cleveland.  One depicts the "Pyramid of the Capitalist System", a common motif of the party and radical politics.  The second image, "The Last Strike", is less typical and rather complex in style and symbolism.</description>
	</image>
	<image>
		<title>Last strike</title>
		<url>images/Last strike.jpg</url>
		<description>The Socialist Party was a highly visible part of Cleveland's political scene during the late nineteenth and early twentieth centuries.  These two prints, both dating from 1912, were issued by the International Publishing Company in Cleveland.  One depicts the &quot;Pyramid of the Capitalist System&quot;, a common motif of the party and radical politics.  The second image, &quot;The Last Strike&quot;, is less typical and rather complex in style and symbolism.</description>
	</image>
	<image>
		<title>First Church of Christ</title>
		<url>images/First Church of Christ.jpg</url>
		<description>The First Church of Christ Scientist on Overlook Road is one of the most significant works designed by Walker and Weeks of Cleveland.  The two renderings show the exteriors of the main auditorium of the church and its landmark tower.   Architectural historians have noted that the auditorium's design, in part, mirrors that of Severance Hall, which was also designed by the firm.  Both structures opened in 1931. Today the building serves as the headquarters for Nottingham-Spirk design associates.</description>
	</image>
	<image>
		<title>First Church of Christ Tower</title> 
		<url>images/First Church of Christ Tower.jpg</url>
		<description>The First Church of Christ Scientist on Overlook Road is one of the most significant works designed by Walker and Weeks of Cleveland.  The two renderings show the exteriors of the main auditorium of the church and its landmark tower.   Architectural historians have noted that the auditorium's design, in part, mirrors that of Severance Hall, which was also designed by the firm.  Both structures opened in 1931. Today the building serves as the headquarters for Nottingham-Spirk design associates.</description>
	</image>
	<image>
		<title>Brush Electric Company</title>
		<url>images/Brush Electric Company.jpg</url>
		<description>This lithograph depicts the Brush Electric Company plant at what is now Commerce and E. 45th St. in Cleveland.   Formed by Charles F. Brush (1849-1929) in 1880 the company produced the dynamos and arc lighting systems which he had invented.  Brush Electric would eventually merge with Edison General Electric to form the General Electric Co.</description>
	</image>
	<image>
		<title>Operative Society Bricklayers</title>
		<url>images/Operative Society Bricklayers.jpg</url>
		<description>This certificate (1880)  which admits William Feasey to membership in the Operational Society of Bricklayers is both an elaborate example of lithography and a testament to the status of the skilled trades during the late nineteenth century. </description>
	</image>
	<image>
		<title>Funny</title>
		<url>images/Funny.jpg</url>
		<description>James Harrison "Hal" Donahey (1875-1949) was a prolific editorial cartoonist for the Cleveland Plain Dealer for nearly five decades.  Almost the full body of his original work is preserved at the Western Reserve Historical Society.  This example "Funny, but he never picks up passengers when mother is along" is typical of his style during the 1920s.</description>
	</image>
</gallery>